{
    "id": "28611a49e44a4fd68d49878d168740bd",
    "title": "Tenses worksheet | Gap fills",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "c325eec1899e48b090424d33496d1b24",
            "title": "Tenses Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I waited for him until he …………………",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "comes",
                        "came",
                        "had come"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "As long as the rain ………………….., I stayed at home.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "continues",
                        "continued",
                        "had continued"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He ran as fast as he ………………….",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "can",
                        "could",
                        "may"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He was so tired that he …………………. barely stand.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "can",
                        "could",
                        "would"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Wherever he …………………, the people gathered to listen.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "preaches",
                        "preached",
                        "would preach"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He ………………. because he was in a hurry.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "run",
                        "runs",
                        "ran"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Although he began late, he ………………… first.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "was finishing",
                        "finished",
                        "had finished"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I asked him what I ……………….. do for him.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "can",
                        "could"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He said the he …………………. make another attempt.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will",
                        "would"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He rested his horse because it ……………….",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "limped",
                        "was limping",
                        "had limped"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}